(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-13T01:46:53.523114",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
BIRTH DAY FESTIVAL - Takanashi Kiara's Hello! Project Cover Song
BIRTH DAY FESTIVAL
Juice=Juice / S/mileage / Morning Musume. / Berryz Kobo / °C-ute
Morning Musume.
°C-ute
S/mileage
Juice=Juice
Berryz Kobo
Morning Musume. Cover Members
Vestia Zeta
Tokoyami Towa
Aki Rosenthal
Hakui Koyori
Momosuzu Nene
Hey! Everytime...
...I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart! and touch me please!
もっと近づいてほしい
I want you to get closer to me,
どんなことも
no matter what it is...
話してほしいのよ
...I want you to talk to me about it!
Touch my heart! and touch me please!
出来そうもないくらいなこと
Even something that seems impossible...
おねだりしてみてくれていいよ
...it's okay if you beg me for it.
ずっとあこがれてた人と
The person I've admired for so long...
再会した
...I finally reunited with him.
運命感じなきゃ
If I don't feel destiny...
ウソだよ
...then it's a lie!
Now touch my heart!
100年経って地球が変わっても
Even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes,
気持ちは変わらないわ
my feelings won't change.
愛の園
The Garden of Love.
Now touch my heart!
1年経って...
If one year passes...
だって私が邪魔ならもう
Because if I'm in the way now,
良い子の私はバイバイ
bye-bye to being a good girl.
Take it, take it, I'm proud of you
Touch my heart and touch me, please
もっと意地悪でいいよ
You can be even meaner to me.
過去も未来も
The past, the future...
あなたの自由でしょう
it's all up to you, isn't it?
Touch my heart and touch me, please
夢は夢と言うの
You say dreams are just dreams.
あなたの夢を知りたい
But I want to know your dreams.
目はそらさない 夜が続いているわ
I won't look away, the night goes on.
運命抱きしめて 眠るわ
I'll embrace fate and sleep.
千年たって宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change in this garden of love.
愛したがりだって 私が邪魔ならもう
Even if you wanted to love, if I'm in the way now,
良い子の私はバイバイ
bye-bye to being a good girl.
Let's go! One, two
One, two, one!
千年たって宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I won't change in this garden of love.
愛したがりだって 私が邪魔ならもう
Even if you wanted to love, if I'm in the way now,
良い子の私はバイバイ
bye-bye to being a good girl.
Take it, take it, I'm proud of you
Kiarackee! Hi!
I am Takanashi Kiara from hololive English -Myth-!
And welcome to my birthday 3D Live today!
The first song was an iconic, relatively old song from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono". Yay!
Did you like it?
There were some funny moves. It's just like... what am I doing? Yay!
So, as you can see, today once again I'm doing a Hello! Project cover song birthday festival.
It's my second time doing a Hello! Project cover song-themed Live.
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did.
Back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I still want to do those so badly!" And that's why we're here today.
And yeah, so a lot of Hello! Project songs to look forward to.
Also, ta-da! Please use the hashtag #KiaraBday2026! Make me famous, take some screenshots, some clips...
Tell the internet about what's happening here.
And also, let's talk a little bit about the background. "What is this?" you might wonder.
If you have watched a lot of Hello! Project music videos, you might actually recognize this because it's...
...inspired by the music video of a Morning Musume song.
Maybe an upcoming song... Maybe the one after this!
So, we will have different corners today. We're starting right now with the Morning Musume corner,
and then we'll have other corners too, all dedicated to my favorite Hello! Project groups.
And for each corner, there will be a representative backdrop, like this one.
So, please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today.
And now I'm kind of sad because I danced all alone. I want some friends to come and help me perform.
So, shall we begin and continue with the next song? Yes, yes, yes!
Bring in the ladies!
かも かも かも かも
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe.
笑った顔をして返事した
I replied with a smiling face.
あなたがウソを付く合図だね
That's your sign you're lying to me.
二年目の記念を前にして
Just before our second anniversary,
わたしが振られちゃって終わるのね
this'll all end with you dumping me.
「また 一人ぼっち マリコ」
"You're single again, Mariko..."
自分に言い聞かせる私
...I tell myself.
気付かないフリをしていつまでも
I guess I'll pretend not to notice
抱きしめられていようかな
and stay held in your arms forever.
ああ あなたが優しいの わかってる
Ah, I know you're kind...
けど その分 つらすぎるの
...but that just makes it hurt all the more.
お祈りをしたけれど
Even though I said a prayer,
心は 遠く 離れてゆく
our hearts keep growing far apart.
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Ah, I thought about breaking up with you myself...
そう 思ったけど 出来ない
...yes, I thought about it, but I just can't.
会話の中で何度も
Although multiple times as we spoke,
タイミングみてたけど
I tried to find the right moment.
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry.
I might cry...
かも
...maybe,
...maybe.
どうしてそんな風に無理するの
Why do you always push yourself so hard?
嫌ならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't want to be here, just tell me.
わざと わがままをしてみたけど
I intentionally whined like a baby,
優しく笑顔で答える人
but you just answered with a sweet smile.
「もう これでいいの? マリコ」
"Are you really okay with this, Mariko?"
自問自答をする 私
I ask myself.
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Before saying it's over, hold me.
ねえ ねえ 冷たくっていいから
Hey, hey... even if you're cold, it's fine.
その あなたの優しさが 罪なのよ
Your kindness is a transgression...
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
...see? It's giving me second thoughts.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want to confirm our love daily.
ああ もう少しこのまま居たいけど
Ah, I'd love to stay a bit longer like this,
そう あなたと居たいけれど
yes, I'd love to stay here with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
...if our last night is on the way,
強気な振りしながら
then while acting all confident...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry.
I might cry...
かも
...maybe,
...maybe.
その あなたの優しさが 罪なのよ
Your kindness is a transgression...
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
...see? It's giving me second thoughts.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want to confirm our love daily.
ああ もう少しこのまま居たいけど
Ah, I'd love to stay a bit longer like this,
そう あなたと居たいけれど
yes, I'd love to stay here with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
...if our last night is on the way,
強気な振りしながら
then while acting all confident...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry.
I might cry...
かも
...maybe,
...maybe.
はやく 会いたいな
I want to meet you soon...
ねえ はやく あなたに会いたい
Hey, I want to meet you soon...
色っぽい じれったい
Sexy and impatient...
...sexy and impatient.
はやく会いたいの...
I want to see you soon...
ねえ、はやく貴方に会いたい
Hey, I want to see you soon.
ヘイヤ ホーエイホーエイ
Hey ya! Ho-ay-oh-ay!
先に向かってる ROAD
There's a road ahead of us...
止まらないミュージック
...with music that doesn't stop.
恋人からの花束
A bouquet of flowers from a lover...
真夜中届くメール
...and mail arriving in the middle of the night.
女の子なら誰でも思う
Every girl dreams of...
HAPPY END STORY HAPPY END STORY
...a happy ending story, a happy ending story.
やさしくされりゃうれしいけど
It's nice to be treated gently, but...
限りなく求めちゃう
...I end up wanting so much more.
色っぽい キューピット
A sexy Cupid...
じれったい キスもっと
...makes me impatient for more kisses.
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
With a pounding heart on this Sexy Island,
笑ってる星も
...even the smiling stars...
気取ってる午後も
...and the pretentious afternoon...
この愛を見届けてほしい
...I want them to witness this love.
ヘイヤ ホーエイホーエイ
Hey ya! Ho-ay-oh-ay!
海が輝いて ジェラシー
The sparkling sea sparks my jealousy,
独り言の週末
...making for a lonely weekend monologue.
あなたといたならうれしい
I'd be so happy if I were with you...
不思議な匂い SWEETIE
...and your mysterious fragrance, Sweetie.
寂しい夜と 楽しい時間
Lonely nights and happy times...
HAPPY END STORY HAPPY END STORY
...a happy ending story, a happy ending story.
もう一度言うわ 大好きです
I'll say it once more: I love you!
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me tight and never let me go!
色っぽい ビスケット
A sexy biscuit...
じれったい ミスショット
...and an irritating missed shot.
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will go on forever on this Sexy Island.
愛して 急接近
Love me and let's get close quickly,
未来に 大接近
...getting as close as we can to the future.
どこまでも 抱きしめてほしい
I want you to hold me tight forever.
色っぽい キューピット
A sexy Cupid...
じれったい キスもっと
...makes me impatient for more kisses.
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
With a pounding heart on this Sexy Island,
笑ってる星も
...even the smiling stars...
気取ってる午後も
...and the pretentious afternoon...
この愛を見届けてほしい
...I want them to witness this love.
色っぽい ビスケット
A sexy biscuit...
じれったい ミスショット
...and an irritating missed shot.
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will go on forever on this Sexy Island.
愛して 急接近
Love me and let's get close quickly,
未来に 大接近
...getting as close as we can to the future.
どこまでも 抱きしめてほしい
I want you to hold me tight forever.
ヘイヤ ホーエイホーエイ
Hey ya! Ho-ay-oh-ay!
°C-ute
Isaki Riona
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
°C-ute
FOREVER LOVE
渋谷を歩く
Walking in Shibuya,
一人で歩く
...walking alone...
人ごみの中
...in the middle of the crowd.
大好きなあの人探す
I'm looking for the one I love so much.
好き 好きなあの人が探す
The one I love, love, love is looking for me...
手をつなぐっていい その思いから
"Holding hands is fine." With that thought...
ふと逸れてみただけなの
...I just wandered off on a whim.
あの人を... この私を...
That person... and me...
どうか離さないでね
Please don't separate us.
恋する思いが マイダーリン
My love for you, My Darling...
大きく膨らみ I love you
...is swelling up so big, I love you.
考えすぎたら マイダーリン
If I think too much, My Darling...
空回りしちゃうの
...I'll just end up spinning my wheels.
まだまだ私は マイダーリン
I am still, My Darling...
あなたが怖いわ I love you
...afraid of you, I love you.
きっといつの日か マイダーリン
I feel like one day, My Darling...
嫌われちゃいそうで
...you might end up hating me.
あ、あ...
Ah, ah...
あなたを見つけ
I found you...
涙ぐんじゃった
...and tears came to my eyes.
少し前から
A little while ago...
私に気づいてたなんて
...to think you had already noticed me.
少しずるいよ だけど言えない
That's a bit unfair, but I can't say it.
最初のきっかけは私だし
Since I was the one who started it all.
そう強い雨 うつむいてたら
In the heavy rain, as I looked down...
手を握ってくれたわ
...you took my hand.
おとなになっても マイダーリン
Even when we grow up, My Darling...
もっとその先も I love you
...and even further beyond, I love you.
腰が曲がっても マイダーリン
Even when our backs bend with age, My Darling...
手を繋ぐ時には
...whenever we hold hands...
ドキドキするでしょ マイダーリン
...our hearts will flutter, right, My Darling?
恥ずかしいでしょ I love you
It'll be embarrassing, right, I love you?
それでも私を マイダーリン
Even so, please, My Darling...
優しく包んでね
...wrap me in your warmth.
あ、あ...
Ah, ah...
おとなになっても マイダーリン
Even when we grow up, My Darling...
もっとその先も I love you
...and even further beyond, I love you.
腰が曲がっても マイダーリン
Even when our backs bend with age, My Darling...
手を繋ぐ時には
...whenever we hold hands...
ドキドキするでしょ マイダーリン
...our hearts will flutter, right, My Darling?
恥ずかしいでしょ I love you
It'll be embarrassing, right, I love you?
それでも私を マイダーリン
Even so, please, My Darling...
優しく包んでね
...wrap me in your warmth.
あ、あ...
Ah, ah...
涙の色
[Song: Color of Tears]
強情
Stubborn
あなたは強情
You are stubborn
わからずやのままね
Still as clueless as ever
もう付き合いきれない
I can't deal with you anymore
サヨナラ 愛し人
Goodbye, my beloved
友情
Friendship
「友達」なんて
Going back to being "friends"
戻れるわけないでしょう
There's no way we can do that
この先もわがままに
From here on, in your selfish way...
振り回すつもり
...do you plan to keep jerking me around?
浮気なら
If it was just cheating...
それなりに
...in my own way...
許すつもりだった
...I had intended to forgive you.
プライドを
But my pride...
傷つけた
...you hurt it
あの日は許せない
I can't forgive you for that day
涙 止まらぬ涙
Tears, tears that won't stop
これでスキッとするわ
This will finally clear my mind
あなたを信じてた
Believing in you...
あの頃がもったいない
...back then was such a waste
あぁ
Ah...
それでも愛してた
Even so, I loved you...
あなたとのサヨナラ
This is my goodbye to you.
動揺？
Shaken?
心の隙間
The gap in my heart
風を引きそうだけど
feels like it might catch a cold.
それならすぐ治るし
But if that's all, it'll heal quickly.
サヨナラ 愛しい人
Goodbye, my beloved.
薄情？
Heartless?
と言われても
Even if you call me that,
よりを戻さないから
I'm never getting back with you.
もう電話は出ないわ
I won't answer your calls anymore,
どんなに寂しくても
no matter how lonely I get.
いつもより早いけど
Earlier than usual,
ベッドに入るわ
I'm heading to bed.
懐かしい記憶との
It's time to battle...
戦いの時間
...with nostalgic memories.
あぁ
Ah...
涙 思い出涙
Tears, tears of memories.
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all!
私も強情ね
I'm stubborn too,
今更そう思うわ
now I finally realize.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
but this is my goodbye to you.
涙 止まらぬ涙
Tears, tears that won't stop.
これでスキッとするわ
This will make me feel refreshed.
あなたを信じてた
Believing in you...
あの日がもったいない
...back then was such a waste.
あぁ
Ah...
涙 思い出涙
Tears, tears of memories.
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all!
私も強情ね
I'm stubborn too,
今更そう思うわ
now I finally realize.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
but this is my goodbye to you.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
but this is my goodbye to you.
イェーイ！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
ようこそ、ようこそ！
Welcome, welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
2曲お届けしました、Flow Glowと一緒に「Forever Love」そして「涙の色」でした！
We performed two songs! That was "Forever Love" and "Namida no Iro" with Flow Glow!
イェーイ！ありがとうございました！
Yay! Thank you so much!
すごい、なんか私Flow Glowのメンバーになった気分だった！
Amazing! I felt like I was a member of Flow Glow!
イェーイ！ぜひぜひメンバーに！
Yay! Please, join the group!
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいです。こんなに大人数で踊れて。
I'm so happy. Getting to dance with so many of us.
まずは自己紹介をみんなに…
First of all, let's have everyone introduce themselves...
英語でやってもらおうかな！
...in English!
え、英語！？できるかな…
English?! Can we do it...?
インターナショナル！
International!
がんばって。
Good luck.
順番は任せますけど。
I'll leave the order up to you guys.
おっけー、じゃあいつもの順番で！
Okay, let's go in our usual order!
英語だけどバリバリね。
English, but we got this!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona! I'm Flow Glow leader, purapula! Yay! Nice to meet you!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona! I'm Flow Glow's leader, purapula! Yay! Nice to meet you!
おお、完璧！
Oh, perfect!
次は？
Who's next?
あー！
Ah!
にこたん、顔ひー！
Niko-tan, Kao-hee!
My name is Koganey Niko. Flow Glow's comedian modoki. Yay!
My name is Koganey Niko. Flow Glow's pseudo-comedian. Yay!
「もどき」？
"Pseudo"?
英語がちょっと足りないけど、ピース！
My English is a bit lacking, but peace!
はい、しゅぴしゅわ！
Yes, shupishuwa!
Big car, big zoom! Yay!
ズームズーム！
Zoom zoom!
キアラ先輩、しゅうちゃんの日本語の「大きい」は…
Kiara-senpai, Shu-chan's Japanese "ookii" is...
英語で「small」？
..."small" in English?
ノー、ノー！ビッグ！
No, no! Big!
ノー、ノー、ノー。
No, no, no.
クラスメイト、サンキュー！ナイトナイト！
Classmate, thank you! Night, night!
キアラ先輩。
Kiara-senpai!
さすがに分かったか。
You figured it out after all.
はい、次！
Okay, next!
Hi! Flow Glow's DJ and driver, Mizutsu Chihaya!
℃-uteの曲やった！
We did a ℃-ute song!
イェーイ！
Yay!
℃-ute！
℃-ute!
はい、せーの！
Okay, ready, go!
うー、℃-ute！
Woo, ℃-ute!
I'm すげーよ！キキララビビて！
I'm amazing! Ki-Ki-Ra-Ra-Bi-Bi-te!
すげーよはそんな共同体意識じゃないかもしれないw
Maybe "amazing" doesn't quite show our group identity lol.
いやいやいや！
No, no, no!
Well, when I chose to do these songs,
I really wanted to bring in ReGLOSS because I know they're all really good at dancing,
and performing. みなパフォーマンス上手いから、絶対ReGLOSS誘って完成度を高めたいと思って。
and performing. Since you're all so good, I definitely wanted to invite ReGLOSS to raise the quality.
でも、でも、何か困ったこととか、難しかった振りとか何かありましたか？
But did you have any trouble, or was there any choreography that was difficult?
全部！全部難しかった！
Everything! Everything was difficult!
え、でもカッコよかった！みんなのコラボ見ててめっちゃカッコいいってなりました！
But it was so cool! Watching everyone collaborate made me think, "That's so cool!"
私も！みんなでどんどん出来上がって、完成度が高くなっていくうちに...
Me too! As we all gradually got it together and the quality got higher...
もう幸せすぎて！みんなカッコいいって言ってくれてて嬉しかった！
I was just too happy! I was so glad everyone said it was cool!
カノンで交互の振りみたいなのが普段あんまりなかったから、ReGLOSS先輩に呼んでもらってそれが出来て、嬉しかったです！
With the canon, we don't usually do much alternating choreography, so I was really happy that we were invited by our seniors to do it!
順番で回るとか結構多くて大変でした。すいません、難しい振り付け...
Moving in order was quite frequent, so it was tough. Sorry for the difficult choreography...
みなさんのこのコーナーは、℃-uteのコーナーであって、℃-uteっていうグループはダンスがマジでいつも難しいです。
This segment was the ℃-ute corner, and the group called ℃-ute always has seriously difficult dances.
ご、ごめんね、でもみんなよく出来てた！ありがとうございます！
S-Sorry about that, but everyone did so well! Thank you so much!
u003Cteと言えば、I want to know everybody's like, favorite Hello Project song! ハロプロの好きな曲、知りたいけど...
Speaking of ℃-ute, I want to know everybody's favorite Hello Project song! I want to know your favorite Hello Project songs...
じゃ、まずすーちゃんありますか？お、お、アモーレ！アモーレ！
First, Su-chan (Bijou), do you have one? Oh, "Amore! Amore!"
アモーレ！アモーレ！が好き！おお、いいですね！最近の曲ですね！いいですね！
She likes "Amore! Amore!" Oh, nice! It's a recent song! Nice!
あと、かなでちゃんは？バカヤロー！おんなじ気分！あいたいとか...！が大好き！
How about Kanade-chan? "Idiot! I feel the same way! Wanting to meet you...!" I love that!
わかる！と、結構オタクと聞いて...
I get it! And, I heard you're quite an otaku...
私の好きな曲はモーニング娘。'14さんの『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』
My favorite song is Morning Musume '14's "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe".
おお！『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』！名曲！しっとりしたカッコいい曲！
Oh! "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe"! A masterpiece! A cool, emotional song!
スマイレージさんは『天真爛漫』と『ぁまのじゃく』が好き。あと『ぁまのじゃく』...
For S/mileage, I like "Tenshinranman" and "Amanojaku". Also "Amanojaku"...
『ぁまのじゃく』は、去年やってたんですよ！大好きです！おお、なるほど！
We did "Amanojaku" last year! I love it! Oh, I see!
りりかちゃんはどの曲ですか？
Which song for you, Ririka-chan?
私は『ソラシド〜ねえねえ〜』が初めて聴いた時にめっちゃ素敵な曲だなと思って！Buono!ですね！
For me, when I first heard "Solala-Do ~Nee Nee~", I thought it was such a wonderful song! That's Buono!, right!
それも、Buono!好き！みんな大好きなBuono!ですね！と、ビビワンは？はい！ビビワン！
I love Buono! too! The Buono! everyone loves, right! And Vivi-one? Yes, Vivi-one!
チュ、チュ、チュ、サマーパーティー！キアラ先輩と一緒にチュッチュしたい！
"Chu, chu, chu, Summer Party!" I want to go 'chu-chu' with Kiara-senpai!
やめて！騙されないでください！可愛いw でも、このいろんな曲名聞くだけで、
Stop! Please don't be tricked! So cute lol. But just hearing all these song titles,
このハロプロカバーソングライブ、何度も何度もやりたいですけど、とりあえずは、あの、まだまだあります！
makes me want to do this Hello Project cover song live over and over, but for now, we still have more!
u003Cteの次に、他のパートも、他のグループもありますので、えー、次のパートに行きましょう！ReGLOSSのみんな、ありがとう！
After ℃-ute, we also have other parts and other groups, so let's go to the next part! Thank you to everyone from ReGLOSS!
ありがとう！ということで、Let's go to the next corner！
Thank you! And with that, Let's go to the next corner!
S/mileage
戌神ころね
[Inugami Korone]
兎田ぺこら
[Usada Pekora]
ワトソン・アメリア
[Watson Amelia]
S/mileage
ワッホー！
Wahoo!
ワ、ワ、ワ、ワッホー！
Wa, wa, wa, wahoo!
いまだかつてないような
It's like nothing I've ever experienced before
キラキラした毎日
Every day is sparkling
ぶっちゃけ有頂天な日々送ってる
Frankly, each day is ecstatic
ワ、ワ、ワ、ワッホー！
Wa, wa, wa, wahoo!
恋をしたら勉強が
After I fell in love, my studies
手につかない毎日
Every day, I can't focus on them
恋のせいにしてちゃって...
Should I blame love...
ないっ！
No!
今日はデート 彼と10時に待ち合わせしてるの
Today's a date, I'm meeting him at 10 o'clock
今日 香りを少し
Today, I changed my perfume a little
変えた事気付くかしら 君は
Will you notice? Will you?
ドクターストップがかかる程「恋落ち」してるわ
As though I'm following doctor's orders, I'm "falling in love"
大好きが止まらない
I can't stop loving you
Oh love me love me love me, love me love me do!
カルチャーショックを起こす程 時代を変えるわ
Enough to cause a culture shock, the times are changing
スポットライトを浴びる二人
The two of us bathed in the spotlight
口づけをしましょう
Let's kiss!
I love you!
女の子には秘密の恋のボタンがあるのよ
Girls have a secret love button
今年の夏は負けない 去年みたいに弱気じゃない
I won't lose this summer, I'm not weak like last year
あぁ 夏がまた来る 胸が騒ぐ
Ah, summer comes again, my heart is racing
あぁ 夏がまた来る
Ah, summer comes again
実際恋するだけなら誰でもできる
Actually, anyone can just fall in love
勇気を持たなきゃ戦えない
But if you don't have courage, you can't fight
実際恋愛するのって大変
Actually, dating is hard
見逃せない
I can't look away
夏祭り 手を繋ぎ
At the summer festival, holding hands
花火を見上げて
Looking up at the fireworks
「綺麗だね」と私を見て君が言う
You look at me and say, "It's beautiful"
浴衣着て 金魚すくい
Wearing a yukata, scooping goldfish
君が足した3匹で
With the three you added for me
なんて恋 夢見てる 15歳
That's the kind of love I dream of at 15
一人きり イヤホンで
All alone, with earphones on
音楽聴いている
I'm listening to music
意味もなく 涙とか 出てきちゃう
For no reason, tears just start to flow
寂しいよ 寂しいよ
I'm lonely, I'm lonely
なぜだか寂しいよ
For some reason, I'm so lonely
凄い恋 夢見てる 15歳
Dreaming of an amazing love at 15
Summer Love
Juice=Juice
[Title: Juice=Juice]
Kobo Kanaeru
[Title: Kobo Kanaeru]
Pavolia Reine
[Title: Pavolia Reine]
Juice=Juice
[Title: Juice=Juice]
Ah!
ついてくる気が
Do you have any intention...
あるのでしょうか
...of keeping up with me?
ねえ 君は
Hey, what about you?
おどおどしてちゃ
If you keep hesitating,
飲み込まれるよ
you'll get swallowed up,
都会では
in this big city.
会いたかったと
If you're going to say...
言うつもりなら
...that you missed me,
そうねえ
well then, yes,
男らしくて
be manly,
自信ありげで
be confident,
爽やかに
and refreshing.
私達だってそりゃ
Of course, even we...
甘えたいと思う bruising
...want to be spoiled too.
だけど甘い顔は
But we're just not the type...
出来ない達なの
...to show a soft side.
胸の元開いた服を着た私の
Notice the sign of mine,
サインに気づいて ねえ
wearing clothes open at the chest, please.
愛してよ保存
Love me!
誰にも負けず 愛して 愛して 愛し抜いて
Love me, love me, love me completely, more than anyone else!
安心感 充足感
A sense of security, a sense of fulfillment,
それが欲しいの
that's what I want.
抱きしめて
Embrace me,
生まれたまんまの 裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a naked, naked, naked kiss, just as we were born.
この愛が 本物と
If this love is the real thing,
分かればいいの
then that's all that matters.
この愛が 本物と
So I can know...
分かるように KISSして
...that this love is the real thing, kiss me.
愛してよ
Love me!
燃え切るほど 愛して 愛して 愛し抜いて
Love me, love me, love me completely until it burns out!
少しぐらい 強引で
Being a little forceful...
ちょうどいいのよ
...is just right.
抱きしめて
Embrace me,
生まれたまんまの 裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a naked, naked, naked kiss, just as we were born.
この愛が 本物と
If this love is the real thing,
分かればいいの
then that's all that matters.
この愛が 本物と
So I can know...
分かるように KISSして
...that this love is the real thing, kiss me.
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up! Mi Amore
盛れ！
Glam up!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up! Mi Amore
盛れ！
Glam up!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore
一番の私を見て
Look at me at my absolute best.
ありのままだなんて 愛してあげない
I won't love you for just being ordinary,
火花みたいな今を 盛れ！
glam up this spark-like moment!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
あなたの瞳はフィルター
Your eyes are a filter,
燃えてゆく空気は刹那
the burning atmosphere is fleeting.
もう終わりなら 綺麗なまま
If it's already over, while I'm still beautiful,
笑っていられないの
I can't just keep smiling.
泣いて
Cry,
愛調も愛嬌も一瞬 素顔で待つわ"
friendliness and charm are but a moment, I'll wait with my true face.
そう、駆け引きとあなたにこそ愛を広げ
Yes, with tactics, I spread love to you of all people.
こだわり抜いた角度で 飽くまでも待ち続ける
At my carefully chosen angle, I'll keep waiting to the bitter end.
美しさの残像 焼き付けて
Engrave the afterimage of my beauty!
油断できないわ 覚悟しちゃって
Don't lower your guard, prepare yourself!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore
私を好きでいさせて
Let me stay in love with myself.
ありのままだなんて 隠したくない
I don't want to hide just being ordinary,
現実以上を手に入れるの
I'll obtain more than reality!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore
一番の私を見て
Look at me at my absolute best.
ありのままだなんて 愛してあげない
I won't love you for just being ordinary,
火花みたいな今を 盛れ！
glam up this spark-like moment!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore
あなたを好きでいさせて
Let me stay in love with you.
愛してよちゃんと 盛れる姿なら
Love me properly, if it's my glammed-up self,
綺麗じゃないわ だって何？
I'm not beautiful? Wait, what?
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Glam up! Mi Amore
私の元を去るのね
You're leaving my side, aren't you?
悲しい嘘だって 嘘は嘘
Even a sad lie is still a lie,
めちゃくちゃにしてあげそう
I feel like I'm going to mess everything up.
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
ライライライ...
Lai lai lai...
Lai lai lai lai lai lai lai lai
M-O-R-E M-O-R-E
Ah!
Ah...
盛れ！
More!
[Berryz Kobo Cover]
[Hakos Baelz]
[Gigi Murin]
[Cecilia Immergreen]
[Raora Panthera]
[Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame]
[Berryz Kobo Cover]
Do do it!
今夜は会えそうにないやいやいやい
Seems like tonight we won't meet, yai-yai-yai...
不思議と寂しいいやいやいやい
It feels strangely lonely, yai-yai-yai.
背伸びをしてるわけじゃ
It's not like I'm trying to act grown-up...
ないのに胸が痛い
...but my chest still hurts.
仲間が集まってガキ扱い
When my friends gather, they treat me like a kid.
今すぐ大人になりたいやいやい
I want to grow up right now, yai-yai!
こんなに苦しいのが
Is this painful feeling...
初恋ですか？
...supposed to be first love?
アーケード
Through the arcade,
走り抜け
I run...
信号が青になる
...as the traffic light turns green.
あの人が
He always...
この時間
...passes by here...
ココを通る
...at this exact time.
ほら
Look!
春紅のスカーレット
A spring-colored scarlet...
我慢なんて出来ない
...I can't contain myself!
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition,
恋の色が か・お・る
the color of love is fragrant.
Yes, my love
Do do it!
週末は みんな わいやいやいやい
On the weekend, everyone's out, yai-yai-yai!
なぜなの あなた いないやいやいやい
But why aren't you here, yai-yai-yai?
こんな日は つまらない
Days like this are so boring.
そろそろ 帰ろうかな...
Maybe I should head home soon...
噂じゃ 彼女が デキタトカ
Rumor has it you've got a girlfriend now...
そんなの まったく キキタクナイ
...but I don't want to hear that at all!
張り裂けそうな くらい 頭が ナナメ
My head is spinning, about to burst.
雨が降る
It's starting to rain...
週末は
...on this weekend,
少し街も 静か
and the streets are a little quiet.
このままじゃ
If things go on like this...
眠れない
...I won't be able to sleep.
切なすぎる
It's just too painful.
Ah
春紅のスカーレット
A spring-colored scarlet...
そっと 近づきたい
...I want to gently draw closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition,
恋の虹が ひ・か・る
the rainbow of love shines bright.
Yes, my love
ほら
Look!
春紅のスカーレット
A spring-colored scarlet...
我慢なんて出来ない
...I can't contain myself!
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition,
恋の色が か・お・る
the color of love is fragrant.
Yes, my love
Ah
春紅のスカーレット
A spring-colored scarlet...
そっと 近づきたい
...I want to gently draw closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
A scarlet premonition,
恋の虹が ひ・か・る
the rainbow of love shines bright.
Yes, my love
Ah
おおー！／いくぞー！
Whoa! / Here we go!
Oh my god! Welcome, Bae!
Yeah! Hi!
Kiara, Happy Birthday! / Birthday!
Thank you! It's not just my birthday,
but it's another celebration because we're like,
this is the first time that we're together as just two dancing!
What an occasion!
How we came to this occasion, you will never know, but please introduce yourself!
Oh, what's up! I am Chaos, the End of Ends!
A stellar star trapped in the cage of life by your best friend,
Hakos Baelz from Hololive English: Promise! Witness...
me!
And, such a good introduction! I wish I had such an introduction!
Welcome, welcome, welcome! How did you like the song?
It was so hard! Yeah, really!
I've done idol dances, but this...
This is so hard! That happens often in Holo projects, but... / I don't understand...
But this, I remember in the dance lesson, you told me about the different genres of dance that appeared.
Yeah, I was quite surprised. There's a lot of house...
This is quite housey.
This is house? / House, okay?
And then there's also locking.
Wait, this?
You said that's rock?
This is locking.
Ah, locking!
Oh, you meant locking, not rocking! / No, locking. I thought that was rock dance style.
Yeah! / That was so hard!
I swear, I was so surprised!
I was like, what kind of idol dance has house and locking in the same dance? That's crazy!
They were trying all kinds of things back then.
But yeah, that's from my favorite idol group, Berryz Kobo.
And it's like a pretty old song at this point.
But it has one part in the choreography that I thought would be perfect for a duo.
So I thought, I wanna do it with you, together!
It's this part.
Oh, it was so much fun! / I really wanted to do it! Thank you!
Okay, um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
A game?
A game of cameras! There's so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera.
So, is this the first camera that we're looking for?
So far, maybe it's like here?
Yeah! Ah! Hello! Yah! Hi! / I see, I see, I see. Yay!
Okay, Bae, you find the next one. Where is that?
Is it there, or is it the opposite?
I found it first! / No, it's over there! Where is it?
Well, if we continue running around, surely we will find it eventually...
Wait! Hold on! Right there!
Right there!
Wait, wait, wait up, I see it right there!
Ah! Hello! Hi! / That was really difficult!
Next camera!
Where did they find these cameras?
I see you!
When is this angle ever being used? / Hello! Konnichiwa!
One more, one more, one more!
Under the disco ball. Wait, I saw their shadow.
Wait, the disco ball should be like...
Huh? Ah, haha!
No... / No, it's like... / No, it's not there.
No, it's like... Ah, it's hard to see! Am I looking at it?
Ah! Yay! Yeah! Okay, okay, okay.
One last? Last? Last one!
Is that the last one? Well, this one's easy because... / That's not a challenge!
Hi! Yay! Okay, okay, okay, that was fun!
Well, well, well... well, this is not the end, though!
No, no, no, what are you doing next?
Well, first of all, the Berryz Kobo corner will continue for one more song because I love them so much.
And, for the next one, I have four guests!
Four?!
And they are none other than Justice! Because last year,
for the Easter Holo Project cover song live, I also had them over but they were like in 2D, in a paper form.
So I thought, well, this year I get them all in 3D! 3D Justice!
Yeah, and they will be wearing like, a little bit of a costume...
A cosplay? Oh, a cosplay! / Something like that. Costume, cosplay.
And it matches the music video. So, pay attention to what's different.
And, with that, I guess, have fun with the rest of the show!
And the next song, which is, せーの… 青春アーカイブ！
And the next song, which is, ready... Seishun Archive!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Time to say goodbye today, my heart is aching.
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Is just writing you a letter enough?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
My dazzling youth bus guide, you are so beautiful.
記念に写真とっていいかい
Will you let me take a picture of you to not forget?
一目ぼれなんだ
It was love at first sight, it's true.
僕がはじけた
I felt my heart would explode.
とまらない感覚
This sensation won't leave me be.
これが恋だろう？
I'm not dreaming, is it love?
君とすれ違う
You walk past me in my bus seat...
いいにおいがした
...and you smell so alluring.
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be so kind to everyone.
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself...
その声 その笑顔全部
...that loving voice and that sparkling smile.
目線が合う度 しびれるよ
When I meet your gaze, it is like I'm paralyzed.
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself!
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
I tell you goodbye, although my heart is aching.
もっと話していたい
I want to talk to you more deeply now.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
My dazzling youth bus guide, you are so beautiful.
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as your bus microphone.
あいつもライバル
That guy is a rival, too.
話しかけてる
He's talking to you.
沸き起こる感覚
I am bursting with this feeling...
これがジェラシー
...this is jealousy.
休憩時間に
During the break time...
少し会話できた
...I was able to talk to you.
まつげがとても長いんだね
Your eyelashes are gorgeously long, I noticed.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Keeper of the clock, turn back time.
最初の日にもどりたい
Until it is the beginning of the day again.
君に伝えたいことばかり
I want to tell you of all the feelings that I have.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Please, oh please, just turn the time backwards!
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself...
その声 その笑顔全部
...that loving voice and that sparkling smile.
目線が合う度 しびれるよ
When I meet your gaze, it is like I'm paralyzed.
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to have you all to myself!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Time to say goodbye today, my heart is aching.
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Is just writing you a letter enough?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
My dazzling youth bus guide, you are so beautiful.
記念に写真とっていいかい
Will you let me take a picture of you to not forget?
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
I tell you goodbye, although my heart is aching.
もっと話していたい
I want to talk to you more deeply now.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
My dazzling youth bus guide, you are so beautiful.
もう一度君に会いたいよ
My only wish is to gaze into your eyes again.
スッ
Spe...
ペ
...cial...
シャ
...gene...
ル
...ra...
ジェネレーション！
...tion!
Wow wow wow wow yeah
どうたらこうたら 言い訳してる
No matter how you put it, you're making excuses.
イライラくるなぁ
You're getting on my nerves.
あの子が好いなら
If that girl's so great...
そっち行けばいいじゃん
...why don't you just go with her?
チャラチャラチャラチャラ シルバー着けて
You're dressed up all flashily, with silver on.
フラフラしてる
You're staggering about...
誰にアピってる？
...who are you trying to appeal to?
よそ見なんて許さないわよ
I won't forgive you for looking away!
好きと 好きと 好きと 好きと言いなさい
Say that you love me, love me, love me, love me!
そう この場で
Yes, right here!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation LOVE!
運命も信じたい
I want to believe in fate.
100万年過ぎたって
Even if a million years pass...
この愛は揺るぎない
...this love will remain unshakable.
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation LOVE!
嫌いにもなれないわ
I can't ever bring myself to hate you.
地下鉄の中だって 愛して！
Even in the subway, love me!
...よりも愛して
...love me more!
ハイ！ ハイ！ Wow wow yeah!
Hy! Hy! Wow wow yeah!
会ったら会ったで どこに行くでも
Now that we met, wherever we go,
ダラダラしてる
you're just idling around.
私が決めなきゃ 何も始まんない
If I don't decide, nothing will ever start.
押したり引いたり なんて器用に
Playing hard to get,
する事出来ない
I can't do things that cleverly.
まっすぐ行くだけよ
I will just go straight ahead!
誰も彼も 驚くような
To surprise absolutely everyone,
熱い愛で 私 私 抱きしめて
hold me, hold me tight with hot, burning love!
Hold on my love スッペシャル ジェネレーション love
Hold on my love! Special Generation love!
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even after passing Ikebukuro,
この愛は 永遠
this love will last forever.
スッペシャル ジェネレーション love
Special Generation love!
離れない離さない
We won't drift apart, I won't let go.
昨日よりも今よりも
More than yesterday, more than now...
また明日も あ・い・し・て！
love me tomorrow too!
ハイ！ Wow wow yeah!
Hy! Wow wow yeah!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション love
Special Generation love!
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
池袋過ぎたって
Even after passing Ikebukuro,
この愛は 永遠
this love will last forever.
スッペシャル ジェネレーション love
Special Generation love!
離れない離さない
We won't drift apart, I won't let go.
昨日よりも今よりも
More than yesterday, more than now...
また明日も あ・い・し・て！
love me tomorrow too!
ハイ！ ハイ！
Hy! Hy!
ハイ！ Wow wow yeah!
Hy! Wow wow yeah!
ハイ！ ハイ！
Hy! Hy!
スッ！ペッ！スッペシャル ジェネレーション！
S-P-Special Generation!
Thank you so much everybody!
Thank you for coming! Thank you for watching!
Bye bye!
One more!
Kaboof!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!
Announcement, announcement! Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
Here is the banner.
First of all, the big item that is the main character is...
...抱き枕だー！
...a body pillow cover!
I finally did it! After so many years of doing merchandise, I might be running out of ideas a little bit, so...
...I did something that originally I never thought I would do.
KFP, don't leave me hanging. Leave me... laying on the bed. Yeah!
１つ目のアイテムはなんと！一生やらないと思ってたんですけど...
The first item is actually...! I thought I would never do this in my life...
やっぱりここまで活動するともう出すしかなかった。抱き枕です！いぇーい！
...but after being active for this long, I had to release it. A body pillow cover! Yay!
Next, we have a really cute plushie set...
...of my kitty cat babies: Smoothie and Chonkers!
They are so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now, and you should too!
You can hang them on your bag or keys.
２つ目のアイテムは、そうですね、私の、猫たちのぬいぐるみセットで...
The second item is, yes, a plushie set of my cats...
キーチェーンなどとして使えます。どこにでも連れてってあげてください。
...and they can be used as keychains. Please take them with you everywhere!
Next one is these badges, but they are a bit unusual because this time they are square...
...and made from fake leather, so they're a bit squishy.
And of course, you can make an ita-bag with these, too.
今回のバッジはなんと、えーっと、フェイクレザーでできてますし、あと四角だし...
These badges are actually made of fake leather, and they are square...
変わっておりますが、もちろんこれでも痛バッグとかできたりしますよ。
...which is unique, but of course you can use them to make an ita-bag!
Last item is the smartphone ring, modeled after KFP chickens!
Maybe this way, holding your phones won't be as hard with your wings. Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング！もちろんKFPモチーフです！<
The last item is a smartphone ring! Of course, it features a KFP motif!
And besides that, there's also a voice pack.
I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months, so make sure to get this one. Rare!
その他には久しぶりにボイスもあります！
Other than that, there is also a voice pack after a long time!
最近あんまり参加してないので、ぜひこの機会に、お願いします！
I haven't done many lately, so please take this opportunity to get it!
If you get the full set, then you receive
a Polaroid from me alongside it, and if you're lucky
to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands.
もちろん、いつも通りフルセットゲットすると、えー、ま、チェキ付いてきます！
Of course, as always, if you get the full set, you'll get an instant photo!
限定版だとキアラのサイン入りですね！
If it's the limited edition, it will be signed by Kiara!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you in advance!
One more thing before we end, I have a...
super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
It's a collaboration with some cuties that might be familiar to you, IDJ!
Yay, IDJ!
この後は韓国のVTuberアイドルIDJとのコラボ...
After this, a collaboration song cover video with IDJ,
『歌ってみた』プレミア公開しますので、見てください！
the Korean VTuber idol group, will be premiered, so please watch it!
I will try my best to raid you into it, but if...
it does not work out, please make your way there on your own!
Besides that, thank you so much for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this, and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merchandise!
In German, we say: Auf Wiedersehen!
最後に、今日は、お誕生日お祝いに来てくれてありがとうございました！
Lastly, thank you so much for coming to celebrate my birthday today!
本当にいろいろ努力してきたのです！
I really put a lot of effort into this!
コメント、いいね、そしてもしよかったらグッズもよろしくお願いいたします！
Please leave a comment, a like, and if you can, check out the merch!
ではでは、Auf Wiedersehen!
Well then, Auf Wiedersehen!
See you in the song cover!